themag.co.uk 2019-12-31

# The Mag Privacy Policy | NUFC The Mag

We use Ezoic to provide personalization and analytic services on this website, as such Ezoic's privacy policy is in effect and can be reviewed [here](https://g.ezoic.net/privacy/themag.co.uk).  

_updated 23 May 2018_

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which The Mag Online collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of themag.co.uk and shop.themag.co.uk websites (“Site”). The Site includes all employees, freelancers and third-party partners of The Mag Online.

**Personal information we collect**

When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information”.

We collect Device Information using the following technologies:

  * “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)
  * “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.
  * “Web beacons”, “tags”, and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.

**Advertising**

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at [http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

**How do we use your personal information?**

We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to:

  * Communicate with you;
  * Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; and
  * When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.

We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).

Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (including credit card numbers, email address, and phone number. We refer to this information as “Order Information”.

When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.

**Sharing your personal information**

We share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above. For example, we use Shopify to power our online store–you can read more about how Shopify uses your Personal Information here: <https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy>. We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site. You can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: <https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.

We use a third-party provider, MailChimp, to deliver our newsletters. We gather statistics around email opening and clicks using industry standard technologies to help us monitor and improve our newsletter. For more information, please see [MailChimp’s privacy notice](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/). You can unsubscribe to mailings at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any of our emails or by contacting us at [[email protected]](https://www.themag.co.uk/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#2f424e48414a585c6f5b474a424e48014c40015a44)

Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a legal request request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.

**Do not track**

Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.

**Your rights**

If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.

Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.

**Data retention**

When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.

**Changes**

We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.

**Contact us**

For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at [[email protected]](https://www.themag.co.uk/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#74111a05011d061d110734001c111915135a171b5a011f) or by mail using the details provided below:

The Mag Online  
Privacy Compliance Officer  
Toffee Factory  
Lower Steenbergs Yard  
Quayside  
Newcastle upon Tyne  
NE1 2DF
